Oh, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 42 in this exercise, we are asked to write a function
to add in, you know, at the beginning of the list.
So.
So consider we have a link list here.
That we have created in the previous video.
The first note contains one small to.
And three.
And they are it like this?
OK?
This is for not.
In this exercise, our mission to add in you.
Not.
Sorry.
At the beginning here.
OK.
So we will move the head from here to here, and we insert number four inside it, and we will reference
this not as the beginning of the think it was the video.
And think about that, how we can do this.
For that, I will create a new method called Bush.
So public void bush at.
At the beginning.
It took that data.
New data is picking the data of the new note that it will be inserted and the first step is creating
or creating one creating the not not, you know, not equal to new knowledge.
I'm creating the note using the constructor view data.
OK, then the second step is make next.
Often, you know, as had so it were referred us to their old head.
You know, on the next equal to hand referencing it as they.
And now I need to make more souls that more the had to point that, you know, OK, so I am equal to,
you know, we are referencing it as in, you know, now in order to test it, I will create it before
the printing list and we will use this method that we have created before in the exercise number 40
to 41.
And we will see that result.
So my kid continue to come here to learn data structure, so I will create here exercise for it to be
adding New York at the beginning.
I will.
I'm making this because they would be and one source code in order to understand for what?
What is the method that correspond to exercise for a while, for it to answer?
OK, so Lincoln last thought we need to push at the beginning, I need to insert number for a link at
list that contains data for let's run and see that print print terrorism.
And here we go, guys for one, two and three successfully and that.
At the beginning.
OK, so this is the algorithm, and this is the trick behind adding and pushing link or not at the beginning.
OK.
I'm filling at least, so I'm waiting for a solution in the comments below and any question or any doubt
or any recommendation.
We are happy to see and.